aws-tower-inv-role-gcs-sandbox is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-gcs-shared-non-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-gcs-shared-sandbox is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-gcs-nhs-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-cbei-sandbox is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-cbei-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-cbei-non-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-arsl-share-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-arsl-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-gcs-non-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-arsl-non-prod is already locked. Moving on.
aws-tower-inv-role-gcs-prod is already locked. Moving on.
> c:\source\repos\tfe-tfc-migration-tool\tfc_migrate\workspaces.py(140)migrate_all()
-> "identifier": repoId,
(Pdb) > c:\source\repos\tfe-tfc-migration-tool\tfc_migrate\workspaces.py(141)migrate_all()
-> "oauth-token-id": oauth_token_id,
